<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="settings_strings">
        <item>Account</item>
        <item>Theme</item>
        <item>Language</item>
        <item>General</item>
        <item>Help</item>
        <item>About</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="account_settings_strings">
        <item>Change password</item>
        <item>Profile photo</item>
        <item>Change account info</item>
        <item>Delete account</item>
        <item>Backup</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="language_settings_strings">
        <item>Russian</item>
        <item>English</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="unactive_time_period_strings">
        <item>Hour</item>
        <item>Day</item>
        <item>Week</item>
        <item>Month</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="help_menu_strings">
        <item>How to create note</item>
        <item>Search note</item>
        <item>Edit or delete note</item>
        <item>Create notes category</item>
        <item>Delete and edit notes category</item>
        <item>View notes by category</item>
        <item>View notes for a specific time period</item>
        <item>Changing your account information</item>
        <item>Backup/restore data</item>
        <item>Delete account</item>
        <item>Log in without a password and log out of your account</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="help_menu_content_strings">
        <item>To create new note click the {create_note_icon} button on the Home tab. You will be taken to the note creation screen.\nEnter a title for the note (at least 2 characters), note text (must contain at least 10 characters) and tags for this note (search keywords).\nMaximum number of tags are 20, each tag must contain at least two characters, and the number of words in one tag is no more than two. Tags are separated by commas.</item>
        <item>You can search for a note on the Home tab. In the search field at the top of the screen, enter the word and press {search_note_icon}.\nIf the search query contains several words, then first the search will be made for notes whose tags, title and text contain a phrase that fully matches the search query.\nBy default, the search is carried out in note tags, then in the note titles, and lastly - in the text of the notes.\nTherefore, to quickly find the desired note, it is important to correctly fill out the tags field when creating notes. Also, order of search can be adjusted in Settings.\nTo do this, on the Settings tab, select General and in the Notes search priority section, select the field that will be searched in the first (second, third) queue.</item>
        <item>To edit or delete a note, open it for reading (click the note).\nIn the upper right corner, click on the corresponding icon: deleting - {delete_note_icon}, editing - {edit_note_icon}. In the dialog box that appears, confirm the selected action.\nEditing the note will be carried out on a new opened screen. Fill in all fields in the same way as when creating a note and click the CHANGE button.</item>
        <item>To create new category of notes, click on the Category tab, click {add_category_icon}. Or, on the screen for creating or editing a note, click {add_category_icon_grey}.\nEnter the name of the new category, select an icon from the list provided and the color with which this category of notes will be associated. It is possible to add your own icon by uploading your .svg file. To do this, click {add_category_icon_grey} and select the desired file.\nAfter filling in all the required fields, click the ADD button and confirm the selected action in the dialog box that appears.</item>
        <item>To edit or delete an existing category of notes, go to the Categories tab. Open the context menu by long-clicking on the desired category.\nSelect the necessary action (edit or delete) and confirm it.\nYou can also go to the screen with the notes of the selected category and select the necessary action from the menu in the upper right part of the screen.\n Attention: When deleting a category, all notes in this category will be deleted.</item>
        <item>Go to the Category tab. Select the desired category from the list. A screen will open with notes related to the selected category.</item>
        <item>Go to the Calendar tab. Use the filter chips to select the desired time period. You can watch list of notes created at all time period, at the last year, month, week or day.\nIt is also possible to show notes for a user-selected period. To do this, click the "Select period" chip. A calendar dialog box will open. Select the start date of the period and the end date of the period. Click SAVE button.</item>
        <item>To change account information, open the Settings tab, select Account. On the opened tab, you can change your password, set/change your profile photo, change your login or email, add/change your username.</item>
        <item>The application has the ability to save/restore user data for transfer to another device or in other cases. To do this, go to the Settings tab -> Account -> Backup.\nTo create a backup, click Create backup button, enter the file name and save it. If you need to encrypt the data so that no one can read it, turn on the Encrypt data switch and enter the password (at least 8 numeric or alphabetic characters) in the dialog box that appears. If the password is lost, data recovery will not be possible.\nTo restore the data, click Restore. Select the data file and click Open. If the file data is encrypted, enter the password in the window that appears. The data from the file will be restored and the application will be closed. To continue working, open the application again.\nNote: All current data will be deleted during recovery, so it is better to do data recovery immediately after installing the application. All accounts and notes will be restored to the state they were in when the copy was created. Media files such as category icons or user photos will not be transferred.</item>
        <item>If for some reason you decide to delete your current account, go to the Settings tab -> Account -> Delete Account. All data associated with this account will be deleted. After account deletion, data recovery will not be possible.</item>
        <item>You can log in to your account without a password. In order not to enter the username and password every time, go to the Settings -> General tab and uncheck the box Require password when logging in. If the user has not opened the application for a long time, the current account will be logged out. It is possible to choose this time. On the same screen, under Quit account when inactive, select the time interval after which you will log out of your account. If you need to log out of your account immediately, just check the box under Require password when logging in and exit the application. The next time you log in to the app, you will need to enter your username and password.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="note_search_fields_strings">
        <item>by title</item>
        <item>by text</item>
        <item>by tags</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>